'use strict';

const QUESTIONS = [
    {
        question: "On average, musicians live how many years less than the average population?", 
        answers: [
            "5",
            "15",
            "25",
            "They live longer"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which artist sold the highest number of CDs in 2016?", 
        answers: [
            "Adele",
            "Mozart",
            "Drake",
            "Taylor Swift"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "A 2014 study found which song to be the \"catchiest of all time\"?", 
        answers: [
            "\"Just Dance\" by Lady Gaga",
            "\"Eye of the Tiger\" by Survivor",
            "\"Beat It\" by Michael Jackson",
            "\"Wannabe\" by The Spice Girls"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which country produces the highest number of metal bands per capita?", 
        answers: [
            "England",
            "Finland",
            "America",
            "Germany"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which band is the only to perform on all 7 continents?", 
        answers: [
            "AC/DC",
            "Coldplay",
            "Metallica",
            "The Rolling Stones"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which song is the most profitable of all time?", 
        answers: [
            "\"Happy Birthday\" by the Hill Sisters",
            "\"Respect\" by Aretha Franklin",
            "\"White Christmas\" by Irving Berlin",
            "\"Every Breath You Take\" by The Police"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "How many musical instruments did Prince play in his debut album, \"For You\"?", 
        answers: [
            "16",
            "22",
            "27",
            "33"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "\"Jingle Bells\" was originally written for which holiday?", 
        answers: [
            "It wasn't written for any holiday",
            "It's always been a Christmas song",
            "The Fall Equinox",
            "Thanksgiving"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How many of The Beatles could read and write music?", 
        answers: [
            "All of them",
            "None of them",
            "1",
            "2"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "The British Navy uses the songs of which artist to scare off pirates?", 
        answers: [
            "Britney Spears",
            "The Eagles",
            "*NSYNC",
            "Celine Dion"
        ], 
        indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0
    },
]